{
    "id": "cc5c4ffaa6e549418381e71f9d430a6a",
    "title": "Idioms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It is no fun being a ...............................",
            "description": "A guinea pig is essentially a test material.",
            "answers": [
                "rabbit",
                "dodo",
                "guinea pig"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "My little girl is always as busy as a ................................",
            "description": "If you are as busy as a beaver, you are very busy.",
            "answers": [
                "pigeon",
                "beaver",
                "parrot"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I was as hungry as a ................................. after the workout.",
            "description": "If you are as hungry as a bear you are very hungry.",
            "answers": [
                "bear",
                "dog",
                "wolf"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She was as meek as a .................................. and hence people often took advantage of her.",
            "description": "When you are as meek as a lamb, you are very docile or meek.",
            "answers": [
                "duck",
                "lamb",
                "chicken"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy was as nervous as a .................................. when the teacher caught him cheating on the exam.",
            "description": "When you are as nervous as a cat, you are very nervous.",
            "answers": [
                "dog",
                "cat",
                "cow"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "When we first came to Singapore, we were as poor as church ............................................",
            "description": "When you are as poor as a church mouse, you are very poor.",
            "answers": [
                "kittens",
                "mice",
                "dogs"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I was as scared as a ..................................... when the teacher told me to meet the headmaster.",
            "description": "As scared as a rabbit means very scared.",
            "answers": [
                "deer",
                "mule",
                "rabbit"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He was as sick as a ....................................... when he reached home from work.",
            "description": "As sick as a dog = very sick.",
            "answers": [
                "cat",
                "dog",
                "pig"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Beware of him. He is as sly as a ..................................",
            "description": "As sly as a fox means very smart and clever.",
            "answers": [
                "bear",
                "wolf",
                "fox"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy was as strong as a ................................. and lifted the bed with little effort.",
            "description": "If you are as strong as a horse, you are very strong.",
            "answers": [
                "cow",
                "horse",
                "bear"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There is no point in talking to her, she is as stubborn as a ......................................",
            "description": "When you are as stubborn as a mule, you are very stubborn.",
            "answers": [
                "mule",
                "hare",
                "peacock"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We backed the wrong .................................... when we nominated him for mayor.",
            "description": "To back the wrong horse is to support someone who is unlikely to win.",
            "answers": [
                "tiger",
                "bull",
                "horse"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}